A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Officers of Superior Courts Pay Vouchers, 1809-1823, 1851
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Officers of Superior Courts Pay Vouchers, 1809-1823, 1851
The Library of Virginia
APA 305
12.15 cu. ft. (27 boxes)
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Auditor of Public Accounts in 1913.
Scope and Content
Pay vouchers, 1809-1823, authorizing the Auditor of Public Accounts to pay a court officer for his service during a particular term of the court. These are the copies sent by the court clerks to the auditor. Each voucher names a person or persons to whom money is owed and for what purpose the money is due. Includes payments to attorneys, clerks, jailors, prosecutors, and sheriffs. The vouchers were endorsed by a clerk in the auditor's office when they were paid.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by County, with cities and mixed counties arranged at the end.
Contents List
- Accomack County, 1809-1817 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Accomack County, 1818-1822 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Albemarle County, 1809-1816 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Albemarle County, 1817-1822 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Amelia County, 1809-1816 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Amelia County, 1817-1822 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Amherst County, 1809-1813 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Amherst County, 1814-1822 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Augusta County, 1809-1816 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Augusta County, 1817-1822 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bath County, 1809-1822 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Bedford County, 1809-1817 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bedford County, 1818-1822 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Berkeley County [W. Va.], 1809-1817 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Berkeley County [W. Va.], 1818-1822 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Botetourt County, 1809-1815 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Botetourt County, 1816-1822 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Brooke County [W. Va.], 1809-1816 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Brooke County [W. Va.], 1817-1822 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Brunswick County, 1809-1823 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Buckingham County, 1809-1815 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Buckingham County, 1816-1822 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Cabell County [W. Va.], 1809-1816 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Cabell County [W. Va.], 1817-1822 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Campbell County, 1809-1816 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Campbell County, 1817-1823 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Caroline County, 1809-1816 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Caroline County, 1817-1822 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Charles City County, 1809-1816 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Charles City County, 1817-1822 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Charlotte County, 1810-1822 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Chesterfield County, 1809-1816 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Chesterfield County, 1817-1822 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Culpeper County, 1809-1816 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Culpeper County, 1817-1822 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cumberland County, 1809-1816 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Cumberland County, 1817-1822 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Dinwiddie County, 1809-1816 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Dinwiddie County, 1817-1822 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Elizabeth City County, 1809-1816 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Elizabeth City County, 1817-1822 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Essex County, 1809-1816 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Essex County, 1817-1822 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Fairfax County, 1809-1816 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Fairfax County, 1817-1823 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Fauquier County, 1809-1816 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Fauquier County, 1817-1822 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Fluvanna County, 1806-1816 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fluvanna County, 1817-1822 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Franklin County, 1809-1817 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Franklin County, 1818-1822 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Frederick County, 1809-1816 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Frederick County, 1817-1822 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Giles County, 1809-1816 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Giles County, 1817-1822 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Gloucester County, 1810-1817 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Gloucester County, 1818-1822 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Goochland County, 1809-1815 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Goochland County, 1816-1822 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Grayson County, 1809-1816 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Grayson County, 1817-1822 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Greenbrier County [W. Va.], 1809-1816 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Greenbrier County [W. Va.], 1817-1822 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Greensville County, 1809-1816 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Greensville County, 1817-1822 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Halifax County, 1809-1816 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Halifax County, 1817-1822 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Hampshire County [W. Va.], 1810-1816 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Hampshire County [W. Va.], 1817-1822 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Hanover County, 1809-1815 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Hanover County, 1816-1822 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Hardy County [W. Va.], 1809-1815 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Hardy County [W. Va.], 1816-1822 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Harrison County [W. Va.], 1810-1816 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Harrison County [W. Va.], 1817-1822 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Henrico County, 1809-1812 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Henrico County, 1813-1816 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Henrico County, 1817-1822 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Henry County, 1809-1816 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Henry County, 1817-1822 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Isle of Wight County, 1809-1815 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Isle of Wight County, 1816-1822 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- James City County, 1809-1815 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- James City County, 1816-1822 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Jefferson County [W. Va.], 1809-1815 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Jefferson County [W. Va.], 1816-1822 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Kanawha County [W. Va.], 1809-1815 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Kanawha County [W. Va.], 1817-1822 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- King George County, 1809-1817 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- King George County, 1818-1823 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- King and Queen County, 1809-1817 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- King and Queen County, 1818-1823 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- King William County, 1809-1816 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- King William County, 1817-1822 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Lancaster County, 1809-1816 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Lancaster County, 1817-1822 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Lee County, 1809-1815 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Lee County, 1816-1822 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Lewis County [W. Va.], 1817-1823 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Loudoun County, 1809-1816 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Loudoun County, 1817-1822 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Louisa County, 1809-1816 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Louisa County, 1817-1822 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Lunenburg County, 1809-1816 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Lunenburg County, 1817-1822 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Madison County, 1809-1813 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Madison County, 1815-1822 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Mason County [W. Va.], 1810-1819 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Mason County [W. Va.], 1820-1822 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Mathews County, 1810-1815 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Mathews County, 1816-1822 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Mecklenburg County, 1809-1816 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Mecklenburg County, 1817-1822 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Middlesex County, 1809-1816 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Middlesex County, 1817-1822 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Monongalea County [W. Va.], 1809-1816 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Monongalea County [W. Va.], 1818-1823 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Monroe County [W. Va.], 1809-1816 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Monroe County [W. Va.], 1817-1823 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Montgomery County, 1809-1822 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Morgan County [W. Va.], 1820-1823 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Nansemond County, 1809-1817 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Nansemond County, 1818-1822 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Nelson County, 1809-1816 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Nelson County, 1817-1822 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- New Kent County, 1810-1816 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- New Kent County, 1817-1822 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Nicholas County [W. Va.], 1819-1822 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Norfolk County, 1809-1815 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Norfolk County, 1817-1822 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Northampton County, 1809-1816 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Northampton County, 1817-1823 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Northumberland County, 1809-1816 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Northampton County, 1817-1822 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Nottoway County, 1809-1816 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Nottoway County, 1817-1823 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Ohio County [W. Va.], 1810-1817 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Ohio County [W. Va.], 1818-1823 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Orange County, 1809-1815 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Orange County, 1816-1822 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Patrick County, 1810-1816 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Patrick County, 1818-1823 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Pendleton County [W. Va], 1809-1815 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Pendleton County [W. Va.], 1817-1823 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Pittsylvania County, 1809-1816 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Pittsylvania County, 1817-1822 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Powhatan County, 1809-1816 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Powhatan County, 1817-1823 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Preston County [W. Va.], 1818-1822 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Prince Edward County, 1809-1816 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Prince Edward County, 1817-1822 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Prince George County, 1809-1816 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Prince George County, 1817-1823 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Prince William County, 1809-1816 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Prince William County, 1817-1823 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Princess Anne County, 1809-1816 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Princess Anne County, 1817-1822 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Randolph County [W. Va.], 1809-1816 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Randolph County [W. Va.], 1818-1822 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Richmond County, 1809-1816 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Richmond County, 1817-1822 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Rockbridge County, 1809-1816 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Rockbridge County, 1817-1822 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Rockingham County, 1809-1812 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Rockingham County, 1813-1816 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Rockingham County, 1817-1822 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Russell County, 1809-1816 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Russell County, 1817-1822 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Scott County, 1815-1822 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Shenandoah County, 1810-1816 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Shenandoah County, 1817-1822 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Southampton County, 1809-1817 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Southampton County, 1818-1823 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Spotsylvania County, 1809-1816 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Spotsylvania County, 1817-1822 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Stafford County, 1809-1816 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Stafford County, 1817-1822 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Surry County, 1809-1815 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Surry County, 1816-1823 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Sussex County, 1809-1815 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Sussex County, 1816-1822 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Tazewell County, 1809-1816 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Tazewell County, 1817-1822 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Tyler County [W. Va.], 1815-1823 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Warwick County, 1809-1822 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Washington County, 1809-1816 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Washington County, 1817-1822 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Westmoreland County, 1809-1816 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Westmoreland County, 1817-1822 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Wood County [W. Va.], 1809-1817 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Wood County [W. Va.], 1818-1823 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Wythe County, 1809-1816 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Wythe County, 1817-1822 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- York County, 1809-1816 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- York County, 1817-1823 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Petersburg, 1820-1822 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous, 1814-1851 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Mixed counties, 1809 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Mixed counties, 1810 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Mixed counties, 1811 January-September (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Mixed counties, 1811 October-December (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Mixed counties, 1812 February-June (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Mixed counties, 1812 July-December (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Mixed counties, 1813 January-July (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Mixed counties, 1813 October-December (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Mixed counties, 1814 January-August (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Mixed counties, 1814 October-December (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Mixed counties, 1815 February-October (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Mixed counties, 1815 November-December (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Mixed counties, 1816 January-August (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Mixed counties, 1816 October-November 14 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Mixed counties, 1816 November 15-December (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Mixed counties, 1817 January-June (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Mixed counties, 1817 July-December (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Mixed counties, 1818 (Box 27, Folder 7)